<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>com.avocode.Avocode</id>
    <name>Avocode</name>
    <summary>Hand-off and inspect any design</summary>
    <developer_name>Avocode, Inc.</developer_name>
    <icon type="remote">https://www.macupdate.com/images/icons512/58650.png</icon>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://avocode.com/terms-of-service</project_license>
    <description>
        <p>Avocode is a platform-independent tool that helps teams turn Sketch, PSD, XD, 
        AI, and Figma designs to the Web, React Native, iOS, or Android code.</p>
        <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by Avocode, Inc.</p>
    </description>
    <url type="homepage">https://avocode.com/</url>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.avocode.Avocode/master/screenshots/avocode_main.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.avocode.Avocode/master/screenshots/avocode_1.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.avocode.Avocode/master/screenshots/avocode_2.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.avocode.Avocode/master/screenshots/avocode_3.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="social-info">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">mild</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
    <releases>


/&gt;





 <release version="4.13.0-9165" date="2021-04-01"/>








 <release version="4.12.0-9080" date="2021-02-22">
                <description>
                <p>Improvements:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We redesigned the sidebar in Avocode project manager to make it contextual and consistent.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>New features:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We released the new Comment tool to all Avocode users. You can now see multiple artboards on your canvas, rearrange them, generate comment links, tag team members, and filter comments by type.</li>
                        <li>You can now upload custom covers to your projects and folders in Avocode. We hope this feature will make it seamless to recognize your projects and quickly navigate around them.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>Announcement:</p>
                      <ul>
                        <li>We temporarily discontinued the support of Avocode Write and Flow tools to focus more on the core Avocode functionality.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
     </release>    




 <release version="4.11.0-8956" date="2020-12-15">
                <description>
                <p>Improvements:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We unified the settings menu in Avocode and moved the "Billing and Payments" section to your user dropdown menu.</li>
                        <li>We unified the tools panel in Avocode and added the icon for the Pixel Checker tool.</li>
                        <li>We added an extra layer of security to your projects in Avocode to prevent their accidental deletion. Now, to delete a project, you will need to type in its name to confirm this action.</li>
                        <li>You can now see the name of your open design in Avocode Tools and easily navigate around multiple Avocode tabs.</li>
                        <li>We decided to discontinue the support of the experimental redesign of Avocode’s file management. Instead, we will be focusing on improving the default UI.</li>
                        <li>You can now open your projects, designs, and artboards in a new Avocode tab with the mouse-wheel-click or cmd/ctrl+double-click shortcut.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>New features: Custom Avatars</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>You can now go to your profile settings and upload your own image or select one from our gallery of cute Avocode avatars.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
     </release>    


 <release version="4.10.4-8916" date="2020-11-30">
                <description>
                <p>Improvements:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We’ve fixed small stability and performance issues.</li>
                         
                    </ul>
               
            </description>
     </release>    




 <release version="4.10.3-8900" date="2020-11-24">
                <description>
                <p>Bug Fixes:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>WWe fixed the bug in the app email notification settings that showed notification preferences for project subfolders. App email notifications are project-based and cannot be set for individual subfolders.</li>
                         
                    </ul>
               
            </description>
     </release>    


 <release version="4.10.1-8859" date="2020-10-29">
                <description>
                <p>Improvements::</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We’ve improved the performance of the app and the speed of tools in Avocode.</li>
                         
                    </ul>
               
            </description>
     </release>      

 <release version="4.10.0-8834" date="2020-10-08">
                <description>
                <p>Improvements::</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We have launched a private beta testing of the new Comment tool.</li>
                         <li>We’ve improved the loading and response performance of the new Avocode tools (Write and Flow).</li>
                         <li>We have polished the UI design of the new Avocode tools (Write and Flow).</li>
                    </ul>
               
            </description>
     </release>        
        

<release version="4.8.1-8711" date="2020-07-29">
                <description>
                    <p>Improvements:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Adobe XD plugin:We've improved the stability of our plugin for Adobe XD. More features coming soon.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
 </release>
 <release version="4.8.0-8679" date="2020-07-08">
                <description>
                <p>New features:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Write (Beta):Edit copy in text fields in any Sketch, Adobe XD, or Figma design and share it via link with your team or clients. To polish the final design look, simply pull text edits back to Sketch.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>Improvements:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Figma Plugin:We’ve built a new, stable, fast, and easy to use Figma plugin.</li>
                        <li>Adobe XD plugin:We’ve improved the syncing experience and performance of our Adobe XD plugin. You can now sync your designs via the plugin without saving them as local documents first</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
     </release>
 <release version="4.7.3-8665" date="2020-06-30">
            <description>
                <p>Bug Fixes:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We’ve fixed the banner displaying the number of days left in a free trial to show the correct countdown.</li>
                        <li>We’ve fixed the issue that caused incorrect top banner behavior when drag-and-dropping a design file.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
        </release>

        <release version="4.7.1-8618" date="2020-06-18">
        <description>
                <p>Improvements:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Electron 9:We’ve updated the underlying framework behind our desktop app to Electron 9 to improve the stability, speed, and general performance.</li>
                        <li>Sketch plugin:We’ve modified the behavior of our Sketch plugin so it will no longer close the design in Sketch after syncing it to Avocode. This change does not affect our version tracking tool and the functionality of the Edit in Sketch button in the Avocode app.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>Bug Fixes:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>We’ve fixed various UX inconsistencies in our version tracking tool.</li>
                        <li>We’ve fixed the error that appeared in the desktop app Help menu.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
            </release>
        <release version="4.7.0-8573" date="2020-06-11">
            <description>
                <p>New features:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>Sketch Cloud support</b></li>
                        <li>Avocode is now ready to fully support Sketch Cloud files which can be synced to Avocode via our Sketch plugin.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
    </release>
        <release version="4.6.4-8494" date="2020-05-25">
            <description>
                <p>Bug fixes and improvements</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Added instructions for new users to introduce them to the key features of Avocode.</li>
                        <li>Fixed an error that appeared during project loading when opening from the drop-down list of notifications.</li>
                    </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="4.6.3-8469" date="2020-05-14"/>
        <release version="4.6.2-8425" date="2020-04-29"/>
        <release version="4.4.6" date="2020-04-01"/>
        <release version="4.4.5" date="2020-03-16"/>
        <release version="4.4.4" date="2020-03-11"/>
        <release version="4.4.3" date="2020-03-03"/>
        <release version="4.4.2" date="2020-02-27"/>
        <release version="4.4.1" date="2020-02-20"/>
        <release version="4.4.0" date="2020-02-18"/>
        <release version="4.3.0" date="2020-02-12"/>
        <release version="4.2.2" date="2020-01-08"/>
        <release version="4.2.1" date="2019-12-12"/>
        <release version="4.2.0" date="2019-12-05"/>
        <release version="4.1.0" date="2019-12-02"/>
        <release version="4.0.1" date="2019-11-14"/>
    </releases>
</component>
